https://reiusa.net/company/site-privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Home  /  Research Electronics International, LLC (REI)  /  Site Privacy Policy
Site Privacy Policy
This privacy notice states the privacy practices for www.reiusa.net. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared (the right to access)
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data (the data portability clause and the right to be forgotten)
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
Our site requests information via contact forms (or webforms). Submission of these forms is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose your information.
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request or to perform the below activities. We will keep your submitted information until you tell us otherwise.
What we do with the information we gather:
Internal record keeping
We may periodically send promotional email about new products, firmware updates, or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided
We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of future contact from us at any time. You can do the following via the Contact form:
Request a copy of the data we have about you stored by this website, if any
Have us delete any data we have about you stored by this website, if any
Unsubscribe from promotional emails (or use the link provided in the e-mail footer)
Security
REI monitors web traffic and web server logs using the best security practices available via WordPress and our web hosting platform to prevent data breaches.
Cookies
We use Preference, Statistics, and Marketing cookies on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors. This includes collecting unique online identifiers such as IP addresses, which are numbers that uniquely identify a specific computer or other network device on the internet. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site including YouTube and Google Analytics.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via the Contact form.
Last updated: 5/23/2018
Products
RF Detection
OSCOR™ BlueOSCOR™ GreenMESA™ANDRE™ Back
NLJDs
ORION® HX DeluxeORION® 2.4 HXORION® 900 HXORION® HGO-4000 Back
Telephone Inspection
TALAN™ 3.0 Back
Audio Security
CMA-100ANG-2200 Back
Video Inspection
VPC 2.0 DeluxeVPC 2.0Hawkeye® V2 Deluxe Video Borescope Back
Physical Inspection
Inspection ToolkitUltraviolet Inspection Back
REQUEST A PRICE QUOTEDOWNLOAD FULL LINE BROCHURE Back
Training
Information
REI Training CenterUpcoming Training CoursesTraining InstructorsTrainee Information Back
Level 1 Training Courses
Countermeasures Core ConceptsSpanish Training Package Back
Level 2 Training Courses
RF OSCORMESATALAN Telephone CountermeasuresANDRE Back
Level 3 Training Courses
RF CertificationTALAN CertificationAdvanced Equipment UseVoIP Plus+Spanish VoIP Plus+ Back
Online Seminars
ANDRE SeminarBasic Telephony Security SeminarGPS Tracking Device SeminarIntroduction to VoIP SeminarMESA SeminarORION SeminarOSCOR SeminarRF Fundamentals SeminarTALAN SeminarTechnical Threats Seminar Back
Back
Support
DownloadsWarranty InformationProduct ReturnsShipping GuidelinesBattery InformationContact Technical SupportFrequently Asked QuestionsDiscontinued Products Back
CompanyContactNews
News ItemNewsletterProduct IntroductionsTech NotesPress ReleasesSpy Stories Back
Search
Back
× Close Panel
